Guide to the Florine Stettheimer Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Printed Material
  - Subseries VII.5: Printed Score
    - Virgil Thomson "Portrait of Florine Stettheimer", 1943 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Series VIII: Audio Visual
  - Subseries VIII.1: Video Cassettes
    - Steve Watson "Prepare for Saints: The Making of a Modern Opera", Connecticut Public Television, [n.d.], (2 copies ) (Box 7)